Mr. President.
I found the TV remote.
Good work, Sergeant.
I'm awarding you the Purple Heart.
But I wasn't injured.
Ow!
Well, enough governing.
It's Saturday morning, damn it.
Let's watch some cartoons.
It's time to fall into...
the Futurama and Friends
Saturday Morning Fun Pit!
Here comes Bendee-Boo
and the Mystery Crew!
Bendee, Bendee-Boo, what's wrong with you?
You're such a lousy mascot
No one understands a single word you say
Not even the jerk in the ascot
Rite my riny retal rass!
It sure was nice of your nephew
to invite us to his cloning lab
here in the Repeating Forest.
Uh-huh. Hey, like, here's a puzzler.
How old are we on a scale of 14 to 32?
Did anyone else hear that weird laugh?
It's spooky.
It doesn't seem to correspond
to anything funny happening.
I'll say.
Turn around.
Go away.
Do it now.
Rikes!
Splinkies! What was that?
I don't know. It's a mystery.
Like, I've got a bigger mystery.
How am I going to fill my hungry stomach?
Yeah. Where can we find food
here in the woods?
How about that kabuki theater?
Like, where there's a kabuki theater,
there's a concession stand.
Say, Fry, why do you
always have the munchies?
And also your eyes are bloodshot,
you're paranoid,
and the van has a skunky odor.
Search me.
No, don't. I'm carrying.
I do enjoy a well-buttered floor.
George Takei?
Reorge Rakei?
Sorry to haunt you so effectively.
I thought you kids were that Dragon Ghost
that's been spooking the town.
Like, what's the story with the yakitori?
Help yourselves.
But I warn you,
that chicken is over a year old.
Why is the food in your concession stand
so old, Mr. Takei?
You see, Amy, this used to be
the most popular kabuki theater
in the entire outskirts of town.
But people stopped coming after they built
that darned basketball arena.
Now everybody likes basketball
instead of kabuki.
It's an insult to my Japanese heritage.
How so? This is America, not Japan.
Maybe so. I'm not sure.
Now, how many tickets would you like
for the show?
Like, none.
But thanks for the yucky-tori.
Another grave insult to my ancestry.
Nu?
Is this the Professor's cloning lab?
Cloning is a sin against nature!
But yes.
Follow me to the Professor's cloning room.
You see, I'm his butler.
Ah, my uncle Fry
and his mystery-solving friends.
Perhaps you can make sense of the...
What is it
that's been haunting us, Zoidberg?
Ghost.
Now then, let me show you my lab.
This is my cloning machine.
This is where I keep
various lengths of wire.
And those are the Harlem Globetrotters.
- The Globetrotters?
- Ruh Robe-rotters?
What you doin' wearin' an ascot, brother?
I think it looks nice.
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
What are you Globetrotters doing here?
We're in town for the big game.
And we stopped by
to help our friend, the Professor,
with his cloning machine.
Just call me
the Clone Prince of Basketball.
Like, it's basketball superstar
Larry Bird!
Larry Bird, what are you doing here?
Hi. This is Larry Bird calling.
Listen, my agent sent me
that cartoon script,
and I've decided
I don't want to be involved in any way.
Nice to meet you, Larry Bird.
Okay, let's clone us
a whole team of Larry Birds.
Now we can practice for the big game.
We figure,
if we can beat five Larry Birds,
we can beat anybody.
Cloning is wrong. It's wrong, I say!
Oh, I just hope
that mysterious Dragon Ghost
doesn't show up at the lab again.
But why would a ghost wanna stop
the Globetrotters from practising?
And against a team of clones, no less.
Well, gang, it looks like we've got
more of the same mystery on our hands.
Like, the real mystery is how I'm gonna
get any sleep with all this noise.
I need some air.
It's me, the Dragon Ghost.
We met before.
Like, yikes!
It's time to spring into action, gang.
Okay...
Rabbit goes around the tree...
there.
All right, it's time to get to the bottom
of what, at this point,
can only be called a mystery.
Let's split up.
Eight of us will stay here
with this dragon trap the Professor built.
Meanwhile, Fry, Bendee,
you go look for the dragon.
Like, you guys are terrible friends
for always sending us to our deaths.
I'm not going.
Re reither!
Would you do it for a Bendee Brew?
Ro-kay.
Ri'm a ralcoholic.
Yummy, yummy, yummy
I got love in my tummy
And I feel like a-lovin' you
Love, you're such a sweet thing
Good enough to eat thing
And that's just a-what I'm gonna do
Ooh, love to hold you
Ooh, love to kiss you
Ooh, love, I love it so
Ooh, love, you're sweeter
Sweeter than sugar
Ooh, love, I won't let you go...
All right, gang.
I think we have all the clues we need
to solve the mystery
of the haunted cloning machine.
Only one person took issue
with the ethical ramifications of cloning
and also had access to this castle.
The butler, Dr. Zoidberg!
Let's see who this so-called butler
really is.
Oops. Never mind.
Here, take this.
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
May he rest in peace.
Hey, there's a dragon in this trap!
Help. Help.
Let's see who this Dragon Ghost really is.
George Takei?
That's right.
And I would never have
gotten away with it,
regardless of you meddling kids.
But, like, that Dragon Ghost
was hovering and translucent.
Yes. You see, I used the projector
from my kabuki theater.
But kabuki theaters
don't have a projector.
Some do.
It all makes sense.
He knew that if he scared
the Globetrotters away
from the big basketball game,
disappointed fans would flock
to his kabuki theater.
Of course!
No, that's not why I did it.
Then, like, why did you do it?
I'm mentally ill.
Thanks for helping solve the mystery.
After practising against five Larry Birds,
we're ready for anything.
And now,
introducing the opponents...
six Larry Birds!
Bendee-bendee-boo!
What's all this ruckus?
People live here, you know.
Mr. President, our children are fat
and dumb, and we blame cartoons.
It's time to get government
onto our backs.
We demand you regulate
children's programming
and force the writers
to shoehorn in helpful lessons.
Fine, fine. Get off my lawn.
I'll have Agnew put in a call
to Hollywood.
All right, let's laugh and learn.
And now,
the showthat teaches kids
to eat right and have a good time,
all whiletolerating others.
This will shut up those whining hippies.
Stay tuned
for Purpleberry Pond.
Purpleberry Pond is fun for young and old
When healthy juicy purpleberries
fill your bowl
We all get along and we're happy and merry
I must get my hands
on those healthy purpleberries!
Bort.
Of eating right we are very fond
When we eat together on Purpleberry Pond
Good morning, Princess Purpleberry.
Isn't it a lovely morning?
It's particularly purp-tacular.
It's pur-practically pur-perfect.
It's funny how we never get tired
of the word "purple."
Never.
And it's all thanks to a balanced diet,
composed of nothing but purpleberries.
I must get my hands
on those healthy purpleberries!
Bort.
Purpleberry Pond
will returnafter these messages.
Hey, Mickey, you seem kind of down.
You should try some sugar-blasted
Purpleberry Puffs.
My sugar-blasted purpleberries
are triple-soaked in maple-flavored syrup
to start your day with Purple Power.
And the leftover milk
looks like Purpleberry Pond.
Ah!
Purpleberry Puffs
are the sweetest part
of your complete breakfast,
along with juice, toast, ham,
eggs, bacon, milk, cheese, liver, waffles,
and a big horse vitamin.
And now, back to our show.
Healthy, healthy, healthy, healthy
Purpleberries are
Eat purpleberries and you'll be a star
Look, a new purp-son
is coming to Purpleberry Pond.
Announcing Lord Loquat.
I wonder what shade of purple he'll be.
Greetings, Princess Purpleberry.
I am Lord Loquat, your new neighbor.
You're coming to live here?
There goes the purple-hood.
You're different, and I don't like you.
Wait, it doesn't matter
the color of your berries.
After all, it takes two colors
to make a rainbow.
Shucks, I never thought of it that way.
Sorry, cheddar head.
Look up high where the rainbow bends
Orange and purple are the best of friends
I must get my hands
on those healthy purpleberries!
Bort.
And orangeberries.
We'll be back
after these messages.
Mom, why is there orange
in my Purpleberry Puffs?
As an active mom,
I care about these things.
I'll check the box while you start eating.
Now my sugar-blasted Purpleberry Puffs
have loquat-flavored orangeberries.
Two colors?
Wow!
Bort.
It's a small part
of this girl's breakfast.
Bort?
I have a plan to get my hands
on those purpleberries
with new loquat-flavored orangeberries.
Soon I will have an important part
of a complete breakfast.
Oh, no.
The Berry Burglar fired his snowball bomb.
The snow will destroy
the purpleberry crop.
Wait, it's not snow.
It's sugar.
Yay!
New sugar-frosted,
sugar-blasted Purpleberry Puffs.
You can really see the sugar.
I don't know which I like more,
original or type two.
And now, back to our show.
Curses! I didn't get my hands
on those healthy purpleberries.
But next time, by gosh, I'll get my hands
Bort.
Will the Berry Burglar never learn?
Probably not, but we did.
We learned that no matter
whether we're purple or orange...
Or new polkaberry.
...good nutrition is just a bowl away.
You know you want to try it
So tell your mom to buy it
Buy Purpleberry Puffs cereal.
Buy! Buy! Buy!
Bye-bye.
We'll be back
with more commercials
after these important messages.
Go, me!
They fight for the heck of it
Because they like to
Here comes G.I. Zapp
G.I. Zapp, G.I. Zapp!
G.I. Zapp
is the code namefor an elite group
of heavily armed mercenaries,
eager to murder the enemy,
regardless of the cost in innocent lives.
Ah, here we go.
No one can complain
about this patriotic dreck.
What's that, a rock?
I hate rocks.
What do you stupid voters want now?
What possible objection could you have
to the G.I. Zapp cartoon?
It's too violent!
Ooh, very well.
As leader of the free world,
it is my solemn duty
to put an end to cartoon violence.
I'll have to reedit the program.
Rosemary, have we got any type
of machinery to edit tape?
Oh, you know we do.
Time for Dickie to get tricky.
G.I. Zapp
G.I. Zapp, G.I. Zapp!
G.I. Zappis the code name
for an elite group of...
Patriotic peacekeepers
who rebuild schools
with their bullet-sucking vacuum tanks.
That's what they are.
Today's episode,
"Operation Throat..."
"Banana Split."
What the hell kind of plane is that?
Okay, G.I. Zapps.
Today's mission is to parachute
into Fort Weaponsworth
and take back our shrapnel laser,
which was stolen by our sworn enemy,
the terrorist group known as ACRONYM.
ACRONYM.
A Criminal Regiment of Nasty Young Men.
Oh, that's clever.
I'll leave that the way it is.
I'll show those G.I. Zapps
once and for all
when I fire this surface-to-air...
Warning shot.
Excellent plan, Profestro.
- That'll blow them straight to h...
- Church.
Sound off as you jump.
Freezer Burn!
Nutcracker!
That's no name for a woman.
Let's just call her Pat.
- Waterboard!
- Helpful Johnny.
- Boxcutter!
- Powder Puff.
- Orphan Crippler!
- Nah, pass.
- Incoming surface-to-air mi...
- Telegram!
Pilot, is your parachute packed and ready?
Yes, sir.
Good, because I forgot mine.
Mayday! Mayday! Tell my wife...
I'll be home for dinner.
I, uh, landed the plane safely
next to this naturally occurring fireball.
At Disneyland.
Hi, Tinker Bell.
Ready...
aim...
Negotiate.
Uh, here comes a water balloon.
That's quite a splash.
Uh, beam me up, Scotty.
Yay! I caught it.
I'm hit. Oh, God, it h...
Tickles.
Oh, no. Freezer Burn is...
Sleeping.
I will avenge him, you heartless...
Bastards!
It's okay if I say it.
Just measuring you for a new hat.
Three, four, cha-cha-cha.
Find that apple.
It's down there somewhere.
That's it, I'm pulling the plug.
Agnew, cut to the PSA.
Give me the ball!
No, give me the ball.
I know, let's fight for it.
Now, hold on there, boys.
Violence never solved anything.
Then how do we decide who gets the ball?
Agnew, show them.
There. How do you like
your stupid ball now?
Now you know something.
That concludes
the Futurama and Friends
Saturday Morning Fun Pit!
Now stay tuned for six hours of golf.